

## SAMANTHA INGRAM

# Archaeologist

Email: samanthaingram5@gmail.com

Location: Bristol, England, UK Phone: +44 077 0007 0004

## **Executive Summary**

Archaeologist with 9 years of experience conducting desk based research as well as fieldwork on historical archaeological sites such as Carthage and Empúries. Currently leveraging my greatest skills in analysis, research, observation and conservation to excel in my work on commercial heritage consultancy projects, as well as guiding heritage planning and promoting policies on conservation.

### **Work Experience**

#### Heritage Consultant

07/2015 - Present

Wessex Archaeology, Bristol, UK

Wessex Archaeology is a leading provider of heritage services to a range of sectors and clients across the UK. I'm working on commercial heritage consultancy projects, undertaking desk based research, heritage planning guidance and conservation policy, as well as assessing impacts to the setting of heritage assets.

Junior Archaeologist 10/2014 - 07/2015

Archaeological Site of Carthage, Tunisia

After having worked on Tunisia's famous archaeological site as a trainee in 2009, I had the great honor of being able to manage a discrete area of work, restoring some recently discovered hot springs.

\* More work experiences featured on my online cv: https://cvonline.me/example5 \*

#### **Education**

Archaeology

UCL Institute of Archaeology 09/2012 - 05/2013

**Anthropology MRes** 

University College London 09/2007 - 08/2011

## Languages

Arabic (Limited working proficiency)

French (Full professional proficiency)

Spanish (Full professional proficiency)

English (Native or bilingual proficiency)

## Visit my online cv

